Welcome to Poipet.
欢迎来到波别（柬埔幕一小镇）
You are so beautiful.
你可真漂亮啊
Come on.
走吧
Hey. You can't sell damagedmerchandise.
嘿 货物损坏了可就卖不出去了
Put her in the shipment.
把她装上船吧
Thanks.
谢了
Hey, Dex.
你好啊 Dex
Bring out the merchandise.
把货物拿出来
Don't be offended.
别生气
We have a way of making sureour client are
我们要检验一下货物是不是
who they said they are.
跟你们描述的一致
Fuck her.
操她
Now.
现在就操
And we watch.
我们就在这里观赏
You are negotiating huh?
你是想谈判吗
Now.
操吧
Victor Dragovic is in Jersey.
Victor Dragovic在泽西
Bullshit.Why?
你胡说八道 怎么会
I don't know, that'sall that I know okay?
我也不知道 我知道的就是这么多
Look, Nick, you don't knowwho you're fucking with okay?
听着 尼克你根本不知道他的厉害
These Serbs, they're notlike the Italians.
这些塞尔维亚人跟意大利人是不一样的
Fuck, they're not even likethe Russians, alright?
他们跟俄国人也不一样
They have no code.
他们从来不按规矩出牌 无法无天
Ugh!
No, no! Wait! Wait!Wait!
等等
Where is the delivery?
收货人在哪里
Pull me up and I'll talk.
把我拉上去我就告诉你
- Ah! No!- Where?
不要啊 他在哪里
Wait.
等等
New Jersey docks.
在新泽西码头
The ship is calledThe Cambodian Star.
船的名字叫做柬甫寨之星
Now pull me up!
把我拉上来吧
- Will Dragovic be there?- Hmm?
Dragovic会在那里吗
Yes, yes.Victor Dragovic will be there.
是的没错 Victor Dragovic会在那里的
Now pull me up.
拉我上去
Pull me up.
把我拉上去
Please. Please.
求你了
You can have her.
这姑娘是你的了
No charge, I promise.
我发誓 不收你钱
I'll throw her sister in too,okay? Huh?
我把她姐姐也交给你 行不
Oh, please.
噢 求你了
I told you everything I know.
我把我知道的都告诉你了
Come on. Just pull me up.
拉我上去吧
Negotiation is over.
谈判结束了
回家到你父母身边去吧
不要轻易信人
They say our genes arewhat make us immortal,
我们的基因让我们生来就该是不朽之人
that our children will carryon our names, our legacy.
我们的孩子会延续我们的声望和衣钵
That it is family that givesus hope.
这个家庭给我们希望
I am proud of you Andre.
Andre我为你而骄傲
As I am of your brothers,Ivan and Goran.
你的兄弟们Ivan和Goran也一祥
Means Happy Birthdaykid brother.
生日快乐
My fourth son Jankocould not be here
我家老四Janko虽然今天不在这里
but he sends best wishesfrom Poipet.
但是他从波别发来了他的祝福
My son, Andre,
Andre我的儿啊
you and I have the same bloodin our veins.
我们身上流淌着一样的血液
Here is to many good adventures.
为我们的伟大事业干杯
May we all live long.
我们都会长命百岁
Detective Cassidy.
Cassidy警官
Special Agent Reed,Human Trafficking Task Force.
我是特工Reed 贩卖人口专案组的
What can I do for the FBI?
我能为FBI做点什么呢
Well, you know I'd hoped for
你知道的 我希望各个部门之间
a little more inter-agencycollaboration.
能有更进一步的合作
You're trying to keepthe operation contained.
你是想一人掌握大局
- Stop so--- Leaks, yeah I understand.
我理解你的想法
Look, you know,it's not too late
其实现在还不算太晚
to hand the op overto us, you know.
把那案子移交上来
Viktor Dragovic.
维克多 Dragovic
Ex-Serbian national,now working in Russia.
以前是塞尔维亚入 现在在俄国做事
Thank you for coming in late.
你们两个迟到了
Dragovic made a fortunein hotels and gambling
Dragovic在东欧和亚洲
in Eastern Europe and Asia.
因为投资酒店和赌博而发了大财
But he's also a major playerin what I consider
同时他还是个卑劣的
the most despicable endeavoron Planet E, human trafficking.
人口贩子
Dragovic kidnaps young girlsin South East Asia,
Dragovic在东南亚绑架年轻的女孩子
runs them through Europe thensells them all over the globe.
带她们穿过整个欧洲卖向全球各地
The skin trade'sworth billions of dollars.
这种人肉交易价值丁亿计
Last year alone this countrysaw over 2000 cases
去年这类案件超过两千起
and I consider every single oneof those a goddamned tragedy.
每一次的交易都悲惨收场
This is Dragovic's oldestson, Goran.
达是Dragovic的大儿子Goran
Educated in England.
在英格兰受的教育
Son number two, Ivan.
这是他的二儿子Ivan
Runs the Middle East operation.
负责中东的经营事物
This is son number three, Andre.Isn't he cute?
这是他的三儿子Andre 颜值很高啊
He's a student at NYU.
他是纽约大学的学生
And there's a fourth son Janko
他还有个老四叫Janko
who runs the traffickingoperations in South East Asia.
他负责东南亚的非法活动
Okay you all know Nick Cassidy.
这位是尼克 Cassidy
He's the case officer inthis particular opus.
他是这件案子的负责人
Take it away Nick.
下面你来说吧
This morning we fishedDex Guroff,
今天早上我们在哈德逊河
an informant, out of the Hudson.
发现了线人Dex Guroff
Two gunshot wounds to the head.
头中两枪身亡
Before he was killed Dexconfirmed to me
他死之前曾经跟我说过
that Viktor Dragovic is herein Jersey.
维克多 Dragovic在泽西
Now thanks to sharedbi-lateral intelligence
要谢谢泰国皇家警察
by the Royal Thai Police,we know why.
给我们提供的情报
Better. We know where.
具体位置
Our target is the shipThe Cambodian Star.
我们的目标是名叫柬埔塞之星的那艘船
The coast guard confirmsit arrives at Pier 21
海岸警卫队已经证实它会在三小时之内
at the Jersey Docks inless than three hours.
抵达泽西港的21号码头
Ladies and gentlemen,we're going to make sure
我们要让维克多 Dragovic觉得
that coming to America wasthe worst decision
来到美国是他此生做的
Viktor Dragovic ever made.
糟糕之极的决定
Andre, relax.
Andre不用紧张
This time, your first time,I will be with you.
这是你的第一次 我会跟你一起的
Open door.
把门打开
Go, go, go, go.
上啊
Move!
快走
It's not my fault.
这不是我的错
Janko, your son.
是你的儿子Janko
But you?
那你呢
You are the boat skipper.
你是船长
Where I come from,
在我看来
men are accountablefor their actions.
人要对自己做的事情负责任
Today, Andre, you will provethat you are your father's son.
Andre今天你要证明你的我的儿子
The blood on my hands isthe same as the blood on yours.
你的双手要跟我的一祥沾满鲜血
Make me proud.
让我为你而骄傲
Please.
别杀我
Please, no. Please!
不要啊
This is the police.
我们是警察
If you have any weaponslie them down.
把你们的武器交出来
Andre!
Left side cover!
左边安全
Andre!
Stay with him!
别离开他
You have to run, Andre.
你必须要逃走Andre
He cannot chase us both.
他不能同时追我们两个入
- I want to fight with you.- Obey me Andre!
我要跟你一起战斗 你要听我的话Andre
Run.
快跑吧
Survive.
一定要逃出去
I'll prove to you...I am my father's son!
我要向你证明我是你的儿子
No!
不要
I've waited my whole lifefor this moment.
这一刻我已经等了很久了
I am not afraid to die.
我不怕死
Do it.
杀了我吧
Do it!
杀了我
- You okay?- Yeah.
你还好吧 我没事
Holy Christ.
上帝啊
Mr. Dragovic was unaware ofthe contents of the container.
Dragovic先生根本不知道集装箱里装的是什么
He maintains he never fireda shot.
他坚称他根本没开一枪
And that he and his son Andrewere caught
他和他的儿子在你们的行动中
in your mishandled operation.
被误抓了
My client is a respectedbusinessman in Russia
我的委托人在俄国和亚洲
and in Asia.
是受人敬重的商人
But not in Serbia, though.
在塞尔维亚可不是哦
- Right, Colonel?- Hmm?
是吗 上校
Pretty dicey for youto go back there.
你肯定不想回到那里
All those bodiesin that container,
那些死去的冤魂有没有
did they give you a little buzzon your old genocide days?
来打扰过你呢
Mr. Dragovic was exonerated
Dragovic先生在海牙的国际
by the International CrimesTribunal in the Hague.
法庭审判中被免罪了
He is a Russian citizen now.
他现在是俄国公民
The Russian government have beencontacted and you--
俄国政府已经
- Excuse me, Captain.- Yeah?
打扰了长官 什么事
Be right back.
我很快就回来
- Who's this, Reed?- Russian counsel.
Reed他是哪位 俄国法律顾问
Mr Romanov, this isCaptain Costello.
Romanov先生 这泣是Costello队长
I spoke to the Russian embassyin Washington.
我跟在华盛顿的俄国大使馆谈过了
I'm here to monitor my client'shuman rights.
我来这里确保我的当事人的人权不受侵犯
Really? His human rights?
是吗 他的人权
Are you fucking kidding me?
你特么的一跟我说笑呢吧
You're lucky I don't pokeyour fucking eyes out.
你该庆幸我没把你的眼珠子给抠出来
Let me know whenhe's gone, Reed.
Reed他走的时候告诉我一声
I'm going to wrapevery dead body
我要把那些箱子里的残局包裹起来
from that containeraround your neck.
在你的脖子周围放上一圈
30 counts of murder.
30项谋杀罪名
You should have killed mein that dockyard, Detective.
警官 你当时应该一枪把我杀了
How the hell can you sleepat night?
你夜里是怎么能睡着觉的
How can you do this?
你怎么能做出这种事的
Buy and sell human lives.
竟然买卖人口
Ask my customers.
去问我的客户啊
When they stop buying,I stop selling.
当没有人要买的时候 我自然就不会卖了
Goran. Ivan.
Goran Ivan
The skipper you recommended?
你推荐的那个船长
He fucked up.
他搞砸了
The police know aboutthe delivery.
警察知道了交易的事
Janko.
Janko
Our baby brother is dead.
我们的小弟死了
Father in prison!
老爸在监狱里
All our contacts in thegovernment over there
我们在那里的政府联系人必须
will have to come over soon.
要尽快过来
Russia won't take us anymore.
俄国不会再帮我们了
And don't you fuckthis one up.
这一次可别再搞砸了
- I--- You're family, okay?
你现在当家了 知道吗
You're blood.
你是主心骨了
Even if it is dilutedwhore's blood.
尽管你跟那些小婊子乱搞
And Andre's killer?
谁杀了Andre
Don't you fucking worryabout that.
你特么的就别管这个了
血债血偿
Come on in.
进来
Janko here, he has picked you
Janko挑中了你
to be in one of his movies.
来演他的电影中的一个角色
Now can you say,'fuck my ass'
现在能不能用你那
in that lovely accent of yours?
可爱的口音说去你妈的
Wow.
Get up!
起来
Tony, the Americans,they have Viktor.
托尼 美国人抓了维克多
We know.
我们知道了
The sons, they tryto get him out.
他的儿子们想救他出来
They have contactin government.
他们跟政府的人联系了
They want revenge too
他们还要报仇
against the cop that killedthe youngest, Andre.
要干掉杀死Andre的那个警察
Min.
敏
You should stop this work.
你不应该再继续干下去了
It's dangerous.
太危险了
When I call the policeand give information
我给警察提供线索的时候
they said they would protect me.
他们说会保护我的
We have.Every time.
我们每一次都会保护你的
So as long as you are onthe case, I do what I do.
所以只要你负责这个案子 我就做我该做的
Maybe it stop whathappened to me
也许能阻止我的事情不会在
happening to other girls.
其它的女孩子身上重演
Let's see what you got.
让我看看你准备的怎么样了
Okay.
好的
If by your art,my dearest father,
（以下是莎士比亚剧中台词）
If by your art, my dearest father,
you have put the wild watersin this roar, allay them.
you have put the wild waters in this roar, allay them.
The sky, it seems, would pourdown stinking pitch,
But that the sea, mountingto th' welkin's cheek,
But that the sea, mounting to th' welkin's cheek,
dashes the fire out.
Oh, I have suffered with thosethat I saw suffer.
Oh, I have suffered with those that I saw suffer.
You do exactly that on Friday.
礼拜五的演出你就这样表演吧
You'll be there?
你会来吗
Haven't I been there at all theimportant moments of your life?
你生命中的每个重要时刻我难道没在吗
No.
没有
You haven't.
你还真没有哦
What?
什么
Are you two ganging upon me?
你们两个联合起来对付我吗
Alright, you get some sleep.
好了 你该睡觉了
I'm going to have to deal withthis, this uh... this criminal.
我要去为民除害了
What's wrong?
怎么了
The girls in that cratewere Sofia's age.
那些女孩们跟我们的女儿一样大
At least she has youlooking out for her.
她有你照顾着她呢
Today I stared intoa man's eyes
今天我看着那男人的眼睛
and knew nothingwas looking back.
就知道没什么好回头的了
How does that happen?
怎么会发生那样的事
What date is it today?
今天是几号啊
Shit. I forgot.
糟糕 我给忘了
Thirteen years.
13年了
Look I'll get you the mostbeautiful roses in New York
我会送你全纽约最美丽的玫瑰
tomorrow morning.I promise.
我保证明天一早
You may forget,but I don't.
你可能会忘记 可是我没有
Happy anniversary.
纪念日快乐哦
What now?
什么事啊
Are you even--
你那啥
It's Costello. I gotta take it.
是Costello打来的 我一定要接
Yeah?
什么事
Hey Nick, it's Costello.
尼克我是Costello
I just got off the phonewith the Thai police in Bangkok.
我刚刚跟曼谷的警察通过话
Listen, Viktor Dragovic is--
听着维克多 Dragovic
Rosa!
Rosa
Nick.
尼克
This is for our brother.
为我们的弟弟
No!
Dad?
老爸
Sofia, get back.
索菲亚回房间去
Dad!
老爸
Please don't.
不要啊
Dad!
老爸
Jesus, Nick.
尼克 上帝啊
Nick, can you hear me?
你能听到我说话吗
It's Costello and Reed.
Costello和Reed来看你了
I know this is hard
这太惨了
and we're probablythe last two guys in the world
我知道我们两人是你此刻最不想
you want to talk to right now.
看到的人了
It's the wrong time and place.
我们来的不是时候
Let's get out of here.
我们出去吧
Nick?
尼克?
Rosa.
Rosa
Sofia.
索菲亚
I'm sorry.
对不起
Nick.
尼克
Rosa and Sofia are dead.
Rosa和索菲亚都死了
Their bodies were consumedby the blaze.
她们的尸体在大火中烧毁了
The firefighters foundyou downstairs.
消防队员在你楼下发现的
Dragovic?
Dragovic呢
He's gone.
他走了
Diplomatic pressure convincedthe judge to grant him bail.
迫于外交压力法官同意他保释了
As soon as he was on the streethe was in the air.
他一旦恢复自由
There was nothing we could do.
我们就无能为力了
Russians wouldn't take him.
俄国人不会再接受他了
We think he's somewherein Thailand, maybe Cambodia.
我们认为他在泰国或者柬埔寨的什么地方
Nick, you don't need to thinkabout this right now, man.
尼克你现在别去想这些了
All the guys sentyou this card
大家给你做了卡片
and I'm going toput it right here.
我把它放在这里
There was a funeral.
她们的葬礼举行过了
How much did Dragovicpay you counsel?
Dragovic给了你多少钱
I'm a diplomat.I have immunity!
我是外交官 我有豁免权
I have a wife! Children!
我有老婆和孩子
So did I.
我也有啊
Where's Viktor?
维克多在哪里
Where?!
在哪里
Poipet, Cambodia. Baby Doll.
柬埔寨的波别
柬埔寨
Viktor.
维克多
You have to move on.
别想着过去的事了 生活该继续
There's nothing moreI can do.
我没法再继续帮你了
What do you mean?
你什么意思
Nothing more you can do.
什么叫你不能再帮我了
The Americans are insisting,and the Thai too.
美国和泰国不断的
They are applying heavypolitical pressure.
施与外交压力
I can't keep denyingthat you are here forever.
我不能永远的否认你在这里
There's only so muchI can do
我能做的就是
without them asking questions.
别让他们问问题
There can be politicalconsequences.
这可能会产生政治影响
The woman in the photo,she is not your wife.
这照片里的女人并不是你的老婆
And the girl in the next one?
下面这张照片里的女孩子
She is about the same ageas your daughter.
跟你女儿的年龄差不多大
Okay.
好吧
I'll try for two more weeks.
我再帮你顶两个星期
But then you must leavefor Laos.
之后你必须离开老挝
That works.
可以
Hey hey!
No running I said!
我说了 别跑
I want to put in place a planfor you, my sons.
关于我们的生意
To take over the companies.
我要给你们做些安排
You, Goran, will overseeall the operations
Goran你将负责在俄国 乌克兰
in Russia, Ukraine, Belarus.
还有白俄罗斯所有的运营
Ivan, you will take over Romania, Bulgaria, Hungary,
Ivan你将接管在罗马尼亚 保加利亚
Czech Republic.
匈牙利 捷克的生意
Both of you will overseeexpanding trafficking,
你们两个都要负责
South East Asia.
将东南亚的生意扩大
Janko?
Janko呢
曼谷
Oh, oh, oh!
Not bad huh?I'm getting good!
还不错吧 我越来越在行了
I like a girl who can fight.
我喜欢能打的女孩子
21 cuts, 7 cigarette burns.
21处割伤 7处香烟的烫伤
How old were you when they tookyou from Vietnam to Germany?
当你从越南被带到德国的时候你多大
Twelve.
十二岁
You know, I remember my motherwas really upset
我记得我妈妈当时非常的难过
because she only got $700and not $1000.
因为她只有700元 不够1000元
你支持她？
不关你的事
好事你占尽 分享一下不行吗
那在家照顾孩子们好呢
还是打打杀杀好呢
快点走 他们在楼下等我们
Agent Reed is from the FBI'shuman trafficking task force.
FBI人口贩卖专案组的Reed探员
This is special branch majorTony Vitayakul,
这是特别行动组的托尼 Vitayakul
his partner, Captain Nung.
他的搭挡 队长Nung
This is cell phone footageshot by a guest
这是在纽约维克多 Dragovic的律师的餐馆里
at a New York restaurant ownedby Viktor Dragovic's attorney.
当时一个顾客的手机录下的
...Cambodia, Baby Doll.
"柬埔寨的波别"
Watch the background.
注意看背景
He took a plane to Dallas.
他上了去达拉斯的飞机
From there we tracked himto Mexico City
从那里我们追踪到他去了墨西哥城
where he could buy a fakeAmerican passport
他到那里很可能是为了
for under $1000.
买一本假的护照
But he bought it from a snitch
他从一个告密者手里买了假护照
and you know how these things pan out.
你们也知道接下来会发生什么
We think Nick is suffering from a severe
我们认为尼克现在的精神
psychological breakdown.
接近崩溃的边缘
Nick's plane landed exactly18 minutes ago.
他的班机十八分钟之前刚刚降落
I got lucky.
我躲过一劫
Cassidy's gone crazy.
Cassidy简直疯了
He's gone insane.
他疯了
He's on the south ramp.
他在南边的坡道上
He went that way.
往那边走了
You stay with Nung.
你跟他呆在一起
Get out of the way!
快让开
Yes?
Tony. He in BabyDoll now.
托尼 他在玩偶店里
We'll be there.
我们就过去
Okay, quick. I wait for you.
快点 我等着你们
Be careful.
你小心点
你特么是谁?你怎么进来的
Where's Janko?
Janko在哪里
No Janko. No Janko.
没有Janko
No Janko.
No speak English.
我不会说英语
Where is he?
他在哪里
他在哪
He's at the warehouse.
他在仓库那里
The warehouse, by the river.
河边上的仓库
Where he keeps his stock.
就是他存放货物的地方
Stock?
什么货物
Young girls.
那些年轻姑娘
出去
Okay.
Fuck this, stupid motherfucker.
去你妈的
The man you are looking for,he is in Janko's office.
你要找的那个男人在Janko的办公室里
But Janko not here.
但是Janko不在这里
Get down!
快趴下
趴下
Put your gun down!
把抢放下
You killed Nung!
你杀了Nung
I didn't kill that cop.
我没杀那个警察
I just want Viktor Dragovicand his sons.
我是来找维克多 Dragovic和他的儿子们的
After that I don't care.
除了他们别的事情我不管
That cop was my friend.
那个警察曾经是我的朋友
Last chance.
你最后的机会
Get back!
后退
Tony.
托尼
You get him?
你抓到他了吗
You okay?
你没事吧
You hit?
你受伤了吗
Come on.
起来吧
We're gonna get this guy.
我们会抓住他的
Just go.
走吧
You stay here.
你在这呆着
I'll go check the tapes.
我看一下监控
Ok.
好的
Gotcha.
抓到你嘞
Have you found out who's leaking the information
你找到那个向警察
to the police?
告密的人了吗
Good.
很好
We'll send someone for her now.
我们派人去解决她
Okay.
好的
Never underestimatea pervert.
永远不要低估一个堕落者
Where's Janko?
Janko在哪儿
He'sat the warehouse.
他在仓库
By the river.
河边上的
Where he keeps his stock.
他存放货物的地方
Hey.
嘿
店里还要10个女孩 洗干净准备好
Let's go.
快去
带我吧 顺序是我 我妹妹还太年轻了
闭嘴 想让我打断你的腿吗
你想挨揍吗？
你没事可干吗
想要这吗？
Go, go, go!
快去
别害怕 把枪给他
Stay here.
别走开
Where's Janko?
Jonko在哪儿
You're not my brother.
你不是我的兄弟
You're the son of a whorewho fucked everything up.
你这个把一切都搞砸的混蛋
Father would never!
老爸绝对不会让你这么做
Father says good night.
老爸对你说晚安
Janko!Where's Viktor?
Janko! 维克多在哪?
Hey Janko!
嘿 Janko!
Get it over with.
杀了我吧
The man you killedhad a wife and kid!
你杀的那个警察有老婆有孩子
Another one coming in a month!
还有一个孩子下个月就要出世了
I told you I didn't kill him.
我跟你说过不是我杀的
Reed shot himwith his own weapon
是Reed用他的抢杀了你朋友
and gave it to me.
Reed把枪给了我
Down!
趴下
Tell me where your father's going!
快说你老爸在哪里
Janko! Can you hear me?
你能听见吗
Where's your father gone?
你老爸去了哪里
Where?
哪里
Cheng-- Cheng Chao.
cheng chao
Cheng Chao.
When did Dragovic get you?
你什么时候被Dragovic收买了
Guess we all have our price,Nick.
尼克 我们都付出了代价
Look at the price you paid.
看看你失去的
You should have gotwith the program.
你不应该跟我对着干
You think you two gonna stop the skin trade
你以为就凭你们两个童子军
just because you run around like fucking boy scouts?
就可以阻止这种人肉交易吗
Fuck you care about these girls?
谁特么在乎这些姑娘
They'll just rot wherever they are anyway.
她们不过就是些烂货
And you will rot in hell.
你下地狱吧
He mentioned an air strip.
他说到什么机场跑道
Cheng Chao. You know it?
Cheng Chao你听说过这个地方吗
Cheng Chao.
Cheng Chao
The Cambodia border.
柬埔寨的边境那里
Hold still.
抓稳了
Why are you doing this?
你干嘛帮我
You're hurt.
你受伤了
No, this.
我不是指这个
Going to the border.
去边境
Probably getting ourselves killed.
我们很可能有去无回
- It's my job.- Bullshit.
这是我的工作 我才不信
You're talking to a cop here.
你在和警察说话
There's Min, my informant.
敏在那 我的线人
She's my girlfriend.
她是我女朋友
You know, some of thesegirls are just not kidnapped.
她们当中有些女孩不是绑来的
They are sold.
而是被卖了的
Sold by who?
被谁卖的
Their parents.
她们的父母
Min was sold by her mother.
敏就是被她妈妈卖了
Now I think they got her and they could do anything.
我想现在她已经被抓起来了 可能受尽折磨
I love people with scars.
我喜欢有疤痕的姑娘
We are the same,you and I.
你和我 我们是同一类人
You have a very strong heartbeat.
你的心跳非常有力
There is a musicalityto the rhythm.
很有节奏感
Dum, dum. Dum, dum.
咚咚 咚咚
We are not the same.
我们不是同类人
No?
不是吗
No one with a heart can do what you do.
我们不做没人性的事
Blood money is still money.
沾上血的钞票也是钞票
But nobody wants damaged goods.
但是没人会要损坏的货物
Viktor.
维克多
Adieu.
Adieu
Tony! The kids!
托尼 小心那些孩子
Listen, okay.
听着
You see those trees?
看见那些树了吗
I want you to run and hidebehind them.
我要你们赶紧跑过去藏在树的后面
I want you to look back.
我要你们回头看着
Remember the faces of these men.
记住这些人的脸
If something happens your father or me,
如果我和你老爸遭遇不测
it is your duty to do something about it when you get older.
你长大以后要为我们报仇 这是你的责任
Remember. Now run!
记注了 快跑吧
Dad.
父亲
There is a helicopter.
这里有直升机
You can watch me kill her.
你可以亲眼看着我杀了她
- Go.- No, no, no.
走，不不不
Mister we aren't finished.
我们还没淮备好
Go!
快起飞
Too bad you'll never see your daughter again.
真遗憾你再也见不到你女儿了
Sofia, right?
她叫索菲亚是吧
She was a very fine piece of merchandise.
她是个不错的商品呢
Where is she?Where is she?
她在哪  她在哪
Where is she?!
她在哪
四周后
So she could stillbe alive?
她可能还活着是吗
I hope so.
希望如此
We'll be coming backto collect her.
我们会回来接她的
Don't ever lose hope Nick.
永远别放弃希望 尼克
I don't know where she is.
我不知道她在哪
But whatever it takes,wherever I have to go,
不管付出什么代价 哪怕走遍天涯海角
I'm gonna find my daughter.
我也要找到我的女儿
‘每年有2千万-3000万人口被贩卖，估计98%性交易受害者是妇女和儿童'